http://www.nexans.com/unclassified/legal_notice.html

Publication List
What's watt ?
currently not available
This site uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience. If you continue your browsing, we assume that you accept our use of cookies. Find out on how we use cookies and how to change your settings to refuse them by clicking on the link below.
Find out more on how we use cookies
Continue
Close
Our websites
Select your country to find our products and solutions
Africa
Africa
Angola
Legal Notice
All rights reserved © Copyright Nexans, Paris, France.
You are not authorized to communicate, copy, and reproduce, partially or totally, pages, data, elements or documents published by Nexans on the World Wide Web without Nexans’ prior and written consent.
If this prior consent should be given by Nexans, Nexans would give it on condition that any copy of these documents or extracts therefrom made by you shall retain all proprietary notices, including this copyright notice.
COPYRIGHT LAW
All the elements of Nexans Site, individually and, as a whole, are governed by applicable legislation on intellectual property, copyright law and trademark law. The same applies to the form of Nexans Site as well as to its content (trademark, texts, images, illustration, …). These elements are the exclusive property of Nexans or licensed to Nexans, and Nexans is the sole authorized user of such elements.
All the trademarks on the site are owned by Nexans or Nexans group companies. It is strictly forbidden to use or reproduce them alone or combined, in any capacity whatsoever, without Nexans’ prior and written consent.  The non-compliance with such prohibition constitutes an infringement which can result in civil and criminal liability.
Other intellectual property rights
Note that any product, process or technology described in the site may be the subject of other Intellectual Property Rights reserved by Nexans or a third party. No right to use such Intellectual Property Right is granted hereunder.
Disclaimer
Nexans provides access to internationally used Nexans data and, therefore, may include references to Nexans products, programs, and services not available in your country. This does not mean that Nexans intends to offer such product, programs and services in your country.
While reasonable care has been used in collecting and displaying information contained therein, This information may include inaccuracies or typographical errors. This information is PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS ; FURTHER NO WARRANTY IS MADE AS TO ITS ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, USEFULNESS, UP TO DATE NATURE, USE IN ANY MANNER BY USERS OF INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON THE WEBSITE AND DISCLAIMS ANY LIABILITY FOR ERRORS OR OMISSIONS THEREIN. .Neither does Nexans warrant that such information and/or data does not infringe any copyright or other property rights of any third party. A party wishing to purchase goods should not rely on it and should make specific enquiry concerning the nature of the goods and their suitability for the use to which they will be put. Nexans believes that the corporate and financial information it posted was accurate as of the date that it was filed with the relevant regulatory authority or otherwise published. The posting of such information on the web should not be understood to imply that there has not been any change since the date that the information was filed or that the information is accurate as of any time subsequent to the date that it was filed or otherwise published. Changes may be periodically made to the information herein without notice and will be incorporated in new editions. Nexans may make improvements or changes in the products, the programs or services described at any time without notice. To the extent permitted by applicable law, Nexans may in no case be held responsible for any indirect loss, for whatever cause, origins, natures or consequences, resulting from a visit to Nexans Site or associated with such a visit or the use of programs made available in the Site, particularly, and without limitation, for any loss of profits, interruption of activities or loss of software or data. Most of the information in the site are translated in different languages. Such translations are made for information purposes only, and only the English version is binding.
Hypertext links
Hypertext links included on this website are for information purposes only.
Nexans does not give any warranty, whether express or implied, on the correctness, completeness and/or fitness for any use whatsoever of the information and/or data included on the sites to which Nexans’ website gives access through said hypertext links. Neither does Nexans warrant that such information and/or data does not infringe any copyright or other property rights of any third party. Consequently, Nexans shall in no event be held liable for any damage of any nature whatsoever arising out of or in connection with the foregoing.
COOKIES
A cookie is a piece of information in the form of a very small text file that is placed on an internet user's hard drive. It is generated by a web page server, which is basically the computer that operates a web site. The information the cookie contains is set by the server and it can be used by that server whenever the user visits the site. A cookie can be thought of as an internet user's identification card, which tell a web site when the user has returned. Cookies may be found in a several areas of this web site and are used exclusively for technical purposes and/or to trace users' use of the site. You can oppose the recording of cookies by referring to your browser's user manual. You can also delete cookies at any time and individually by referring to your computer's user manual. More information is available at www.AboutCookies.org. Should you want to get any additional information regarding the above topic, please refer to our dedicated section about cookie policy.
PRIVACY
Nexans considers privacy an important issue, so this Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use one of Nexans web sites and some of the steps we take to safeguard it. These principles apply to personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. By this we mean information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address, e-mail address or other contact details.
DATA COLLECTION
Browsing of our web sites and most other services do not require any personally identifying information.
In certain sections of the site, in order to provide you with products or services that may be of interest, you may be invited to provide 'personal' information that identifies you that is to say your first name, last name, e-mail address, or other contact information that you may voluntarily submit to us : job title, function, country, language preference, business phone, mobile phone, fax number, fields of interest, company name, company type, postal address of the company, number of employees.
Visitors of the site can choose not to enter any personal information.
Nexans may collect limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to better understand user behavior and to further improve our offering. When we require personally identifying information, we will inform you about the types of information we collect and how we use it. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your personal information with us. It is then up to you to decide if you want to provide the information or not.
Please note that, once you register on the site, your data will be stored as long as your account remains active on the site. However, if Nexans does not witness any activity over a period of 24 months, it gets classified as inactive account and your data will be anonymized.
USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA
Data available to Nexans will be used for the purpose of the technical administration of our website, responding to your direct enquiries and may also be used to provide you with additional information related to content viewed online. You will be able to unsubscribe to marketing communications at any stage. All marketing emails will include unsubscribe links or you can request this at any time by emailing the contact below.
INFORMATION SHARING
In certain circumstances, direct contractual partners of Nexans such as outsourced agencies/external partners (e.g. an event organizer acting on behalf of Nexans or any its affiliated companies) may have access to limited information necessary to contact you. At all times we will ensure that contractual partners of Nexans put in place a comparable level of data protection.
Beyond the above, no personal data information will be shared with third parties.
We do not sell or transfer your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances:
•    We have your expressed consent.
•    We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing your request on our behalf in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
•    We conclude that we are required by law.
•    We may store and process personal information collected on our site in any country in which Nexans or our hosting providers maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country.
•    We may share aggregated information with others which do not include any personally identifying information.
INFORMATION SECURITY
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. We restrict access to your personally identifying information to Nexans employees who need to know that information in order to fulfill your request or supply our services.
RIGHT TO INFORMATION
In accordance with Article 4(7) of the EU General Data Protection Regulation we will be prepared to address any requests made by our users related to their expanded individual rights under the GDPR:
Right to be forgotten: you may terminate your NEXANS account at any time, in which case we will permanently delete your account and all data associated with it.
Right to object: you may opt out of inclusion of your data in our data science projects simply by changing the Privacy Setting on your account.
Right to rectification: you may access and update your Nexans account settings at any time to correct or complete your account information. You may also contact Nexans at contact.privacy@nexans.com any time to access, correct, amend or delete information that we hold about you, as explained in our Privacy Policy.
Right of access: our privacy policy describes what data we collect and how we use it. If you have specific questions about particular data, you can contact  contact.privacy@nexans.com for further information at any time.
Right of portability: we will export your account data to a third party at any time upon your request.
You also have the right to file a complaint with a data protection supervisory authority regarding our processing of your personal data. The responsible party in accordance with Article 4(7) of the EU General Data Protection Regulation can be contacted at contact.privacy@nexans.com or at our postal address at the attention of the “Data Protection Officer”.
Links
The external sites linked to the Nexans web sites are developed by people over whom Nexans exercises no control. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.
Changes to this Policy
Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. Each version will be noted at the top of the page. Prior versions of this Privacy Policy will be kept in an archive for you to view. This policy has been last updated on May 2018. If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us any time.
Applicable Law
Nexans this Legal Notice shall be governed by French Law without regard to its provisions on conflicts of laws.
Contact details
Site editor
Nexans, société anonyme
4 allée de l’Arche
CS70088
92070 Paris La Défense Cedex
RCS Paris 393 525 852
Director of publication : Christopher Guérin
Site hosting
oXya France
21 rue Camille Desmoulins
92130 Issy Les Moulineaux – France
Close
Contact us
Topics on which you wish to get more informations:
Company
Finance
Business
Careers
CSR
Innovation
Required fields*
Please check your entry and try again.
first name*
last name*
email*
An email address must contain a single @
phone number*
country*
Select
AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAndorraAngolaArgentinaArmeniaAustraliaAustriaBahrainBangladeshBelarusBelgiumBeninBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCroatiaCyprusCzech RepublicDemocratic Republic of CongoDenmarkDjiboutiEgyptEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFijiFinlandFranceFrench PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGreeceGreenlandGuadeloupeGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIsraelItalyIvory CoastJapanJordanKenyaKoreaKosovoKuwaitLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLithuaniaMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMoroccoMozambiqueNamibiaNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNigerNigeriaNorwayOmanOuter MongoliaPakistanPalestian TerritoriesPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSpainSri LankaSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwanTanzaniaThailandTogoTongaTunisiaTurkeyTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamWallis and Futuna islandsWestern SamoaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
company*
subject*
message*
Send form
Personal data protector
You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data and/or their use for direct marketing or commercial purposes
Thank you!
Thanks for contacting us. We will be in touch with you shortly.
Error
An error occurred. Please try again.
Close
